

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

#### **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and n nothing of a poisonfilled. Until, from a twho, twho chaffinch may also pursue it, not even a of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

## **EDUCATION**



#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. and equal blame belongs to those who fail in t administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

#### FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY

major. corporate administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

# **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult ăm and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

## Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to comes from a line in sec goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

#### **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute

**ACTIVITIES** 



Sep 2003 - 2007

#### **CVPRO JSC**

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer  $\hat{o}$  tình, nhiều khi do cố ý (xen thêm vào' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

### **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

# HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2013 - 2014

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US of text (sentence, paragraph, page, etc.

#### **REFERENCES**



#### **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

#### **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop

Excel English

Power Point Japanese

#### **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt ike men who are so beguiled and demoralized by the charms and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities